<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Darija &amp; Stefan</title>
    <link>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Darija &amp; Stefan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>rs</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>THE WEDDING RINGS HAVE ARRIVED</title>
      <link>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/wedding-rings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/wedding-rings/</guid>
      <description>A few days before the wedding, the wedding rings arrived – elegant, classy, and made of white gold of excellent fineness. The future bride opted for the Burme Eternity Nº22 model with 18 diamonds, while the groom chose the same model with a simple line in the middle, which matches his style extremely nicely. These so called „anatomical wedding rings“ of the highest quality are specially adapted to the shape of the finger of the person who wears them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A drawing of the newlyweds</title>
      <link>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/dawing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/dawing/</guid>
      <description>Ten days before the scheduled celebration, the friend of the future bride and groom Nada Arsenović surprised the newlyweds with a colorful drawing of the two of them! The drawing is done in an extremely original style, in bright and cheerful colors. On it, we can see Stefan, in a wedding suit and with a bow around his neck, riding a bicycle. Darija is sitting on the puck with a broad smile, holding a bouqueut made of pink roses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID19 PRECAUTIONS TAKEN AT THE WEDDING</title>
      <link>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/health/</guid>
      <description>At the end of June 2020, reports began on an increased number of cases of corona disease in Serbia. The plague that we hoped to see back unfortunately returned in the summer months, when, according to the forecasts of experts, it should not have been expected.
  There is no data that there is a large number of patients in Novi Sad and Vojvodina. The situation in the north of Serbia seems to be much better than in other parts of Serbia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The invitations have arrived!</title>
      <link>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/invitations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/invitations/</guid>
      <description>They have finally arrived – the invitations chosen with a lot of love and attention to detail! There are Serbian and English versions and both are written in verse! Although there is also an electronic version, the majority of guests will have their in invitations handed in person because they are really beautiful! P.S. Pay attention to the little owls at the top of the invitation - they have been chosen as a symbol of love among the future newlyweds!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the newlyweds</title>
      <link>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darijaistefan.wedding/en/post/about/</guid>
      <description>Stefan is a software engineer from Zrenjanin who loves animals, ice cream and cycling! He is always up for new experiences and adventures (skydiving is high on the list of things he would like to try!) He wants to visit as many countries as possible and get to know as many different cultures as he can… He enjoys horse riding and fine dining! He trained wrestling for a very long time, and then he played airsoft for quite some time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>